<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<DagothDream_1>In the dream, a tall figure with a golden mask led them among the dead, as though a wedding celebration. They heard many voices, but no lips moved. They strained to breathe, but their chest didn't move. The tall figure spoke with each figure as he passed among them, laughing and joking, as if they were alive, but the figures made no reply. They tried to cry out, but without breathe, their tongue fluttered in vain.</DagothDream_1>
	<DagothDream_2>In the dream, a tall figure with a golden mask greeted them, saying, "There are many rooms in the house of the Master. Be easy, for from the hands of your enemies I have delivered you". It seemed they had died and could see themself laid upon a table lit by candles. But with their own hands they touched the figure, and the figure drew breath, opened eyes, and rose from the table. Then the room was gone, and the world filled with light, and they awoke.</DagothDream_2>
	<DagothDream_3>In the dream, a tall figure with a golden mask spoke to them, but they understood not a word. He smiled, and seemed pleasant, but when he reached to touch them, it terrified them, and they tried to escape, but couldn't move. They tried to cry out, but they couldn't make a sound. The figure kept smiling and talking, but they felt sure he was trying to cast some sort of spell on them. When they awoke, they couldn't recall how the dream ended.</DagothDream_3>
	<DagothDream_4>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask led them through ancient tunnels, lined with strange metal pipes. He led them into a cavern, a large cavern, filled with the hiss of steam, the smell of sulfur, and a giant figure. The giant figure stood silently, unwavering, but in the cavity where a chest should be, a heart made of stone. The tall figure in the golden mask stood before them, gazing at the giant figure, smiling, at his creation.</DagothDream_4>
	<DagothDream_5>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask greeted them, as one would greet an old friend. He led them through a bleak wasteland of ash and fire, into ancient ruins made of a strange metal, into a chamber containing a stone table. Another figure stood waiting, on the other side of the table, the figure had no face where a face should be. The tall figure in the golden mask spoke, as one would to an old friend. "I have a gift for you, should you accept my hand. The gift of a life reborn, flesh made anew, a glimpse beyond the dream that you perceive to be life". Then, the figure with no face breathed a thick cloud of dust, and they awoke from their dream, the taste of ash still lingering in the air around them.</DagothDream_5>
	<DagothDream_Awakening_Peaceful>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask spoke to them. "Lord Voryn Dagoth, Dagoth Ur, steadfast liegeman, faithful friend, bids you come and climb Red Mountain, break your bonds, shed cursed skin".</DagothDream_Awakening_Peaceful>
	<DagothDream_Awakening_Agressive>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask spoke to them. "Lord Voryn Dagoth, Dagoth Ur, steadfast liegeman, faithful friend, bids you forsake your old life, break their bonds, cleanse cursed skin".</DagothDream_Awakening_Agressive>
	<DagothDream_InterruptedSleep>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask led them through a familiar corridor. The figure stopped before an open door, a very familiar door. They stepped into the doorway, and saw a familiar bed, with a familiar body sleeping in it. From the shadows, a new figure emerged, crept towards the familiar bed, and reached out, to the familiar body sleeping in it. They suddenly awoke to a hand reaching out to them from the shadows.</DagothDream_InterruptedSleep>
	<DagothDream_DreamerWakes>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask stood before them. The figure slowly walked forward, the ringing of bells echoing in the background. Hands gripped their head, the red eyes behind the golden mask meeting their gaze. A third eye in the middle of the golden mask pierced their mind. They suddenly awoke in a delirious state, the third eye of the figure in the golden mask lingering in the air before them.</DagothDream_DreamerWakes>
	<DagothDream_PantsOnFire>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask stood before them, leading them through a labyrinth of ancient tunnels, the walls lined with rock and pipes made of a strange metal. The further the figure in the gold mask lead them, the warmer the tunnels became. As they continued to follow the figure in the golden mask, the heat became unbearable, sweat simply evaporating on their skin. The figure in the golden mask finally spoke, a simple phrase that they would not soon forget. "Return to ash". They suddenly awoke to the smell of burning hair and fabric, the room illuminated by an orange blaze.</DagothDream_PantsOnFire>
	<DagothDream_TheLeftovers>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask led them through a series of strange tunnels, to a door made of a strange metal. The figure in the golden mask stopped, turned towards them, and gestured towards the door. They immediately knew what must be done. Walking forward, they reached out to the door, effortlessly pushing it open, and stepped through. They awoke in a place the did not recognise.</DagothDream_TheLeftovers>
	<DagothDream_FleshRemade>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask was standing at the end of a dark room. As their eyes adjusted, they noticed several deformed figures wandering the room. They looked down at their hands, the skin shifting, moving. The skin on their arms bubbling. They felt their face deforming. They tried to scream out in pain, but their mouth could not open. They awoke, their skin crawling under the sheets.</DagothDream_FleshRemade>
	<DagothDream_SleepParalysis>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask was walking through ash covered ruins. They tried to follow, but their legs could not move. They looked down and saw their legs slowly sinking into ash. Several deformed hands reaching up towards them, dragging them down. They awoke, unable to move, the hands still reaching towards them from the shadows.</DagothDream_SleepParalysis>
	
	<DagothDream_Touched>\n\nOf the affected, the following {0} have gained the trait "Touched by Dagoth Ur":</DagothDream_Touched>
	
	<DagothDream_SettlementClaimed>In the dream, a tall figure in a golden mask stood before them, a settlement ablaze in the distance. They stood there, trying to move but their legs didn't respond, as servants of Dagoth Ur ran around in the shadows, illuminated by the blaze of the settlement. Screams filled their ears, the smell of burning wood and flesh filled their nose. They awoke, covered in sweat, the screams still lingering in the air.</DagothDream_SettlementClaimed>
</LanguageData>